A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23 (A94-A97) FA471
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A97), 1966, 1969-1997, 2004; bulk; 1.23; 129.6 Cubic Feet; 108 record cartons. Boxes R2965-R3072.
  - Global Environment (GE)
    - GE 9224 - ENVIRONMENTAL AND ENERGY STUDY INSTITUTE (EESI) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1992-1993 (Box R2979)
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - PS 8913 - NATIONAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE OF HEALTH (ETHIOPIA) - HIV AMONG ETHIOPIAN WOMEN, 1988-1992 (Box R2983)
    - PS 8922 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - POPLINE DATABASE IN AFRICA, 1988-1992 (Box R2983)
    - PS 8926 - ASSIUT UNIVERSITY- NORPLANT USE, 1985-1993, 1996 (Box R2983)
    - PS 8934 - UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN - MALARIA TREATMENT IN PREGNANT WOMEN, 1989-1992, 1996 (Box R2983)
    - PS 8939 - NATIONAL MUSEUMS OF KENYA-ISAHAKIA, 1986-1994 (Box R2983)
    - PS 9026 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - CONTRACEPTIVE FAILURE IN CHINA, 1990-1994 (Box R2983)
    - PS 9029 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI - AFRICAN WOMEN & HIV-1 RELATED DISEASES, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R2983)
    - PS 9046 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - MULTIDISCIPLINARY POPULATION PROGRAMS, 1990-1994 (Box R2983)
    - PS 9107 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY - CONTRACEPTIVE EFFICACY, 1991-1993 (Box R2983)
    - PS 9201 - CAIN, MEAD TAYLOR, 1990-1993 (Box R2983)
    - PS 9204 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION - ENABLE DEVELOPING-COUNTRY EXPERTS TO ATTEND WORKSHOP, 1992 (Box R2983)
    - PS 9206 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - SPERMATOZOA, 1988-1996 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9208 - JIANGSU PROVINCE SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY EXCHANGE CENTRE WITH FOREIGN COUNTRIES - FIRST ASIAN AND OCEANIC CONGRESS OF ANDROLOGY, 1991-1993 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9211 - KENYA MEDICAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - ORAL GOSSYPOL AND HIV INFECTION, 1987-1993 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9212 - CENTER FOR POPULATION OPTIONS - ADOLESCENT HEALTH CONFERENCE, 1991-1992 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9214 - CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY, VALPARAISO - MALE REPRODUCTION, 1990-1992 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9215 - WATKINS, SUSAN GOTTS- DEMOGRAPHIC TRANSITION, 1992-1994 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9220 - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH AND BIOMEDICINE, LTD. - POPULATION, WOMEN AND THE ENVIRONMENT, 1991-1993 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9222 - INTERNATIONAL UNION FOR THE SCIENTIFIC STUDY OF POPULATION - PEOPLING OF THE AMERICAS CONFERENCE, 1991-1993 (Box R2985)
    - PS 9222 - INTERNATIONAL UNION FOR THE SCIENTIFIC STUDY OF POPULATION - PEOPLING OF THE AMERICAS CONFERENCE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2985)
    - PS 9223 - INTERNATIONAL UNION FOR THE SCIENTIFIC STUDY OF POPULATION - SEMINAR ON ECONOMIES OF LATIN AMERICA, 1992-1996 (Box R2986)
    - PS 9224 - COALE, ANSLEY J .- ATTEND SEMINAR ON 1990 CHINA CENSUS, 1992-1996; 2 folders. (Box R2986)
    - PS 9226 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - AFRICAN DEMOGRAPHY, 1978-1994 (Box R2986)
    - PS 9226 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - AFRICAN DEMOGRAPHY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2986)
    - PS 9227 - COLORADO PREVENTION CENTER - POPULATION ISSUES AND EARTH SUMMIT CONFERENCE, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R2986)
    - PS 9228 - POPULATION COUNCIL - ENABLE DEVELOPING COUNTRY PARTICIPANTS TO ATTEND MEETING, 1992-1993 (Box R2986)
    - PS 9229 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - MAMMALIAN TESTES GROWTH FACTOR, 1990-1994 (Box R2986)
    - PS 9231 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA- PLACENTAL MORPHOGENESIS, 1990-1993 (Box R2986)
    - PS 9232 - CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY (CHILE) - FERTILIZATION IN ANIMALS, 1989-1994 (Box R2986)
    - PS 9235 - UNIVERSITY OF LAGOS - CHLOROQUINE AND MALE FERTILITY IN RATS, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9236 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH (PATH) - PAPER ON ROLE OF INDUSTRY IN CONTRACEPTIVE R & D, 1992-1993 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9239 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - MEETING ON POPULATION GROWTH AND LAND USE IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1992-1993 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9240 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION - FAMILY PLANNING CONGRESS, 1991-1994 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9244 - MARINE BIOLOGICAL LABORATORY (WOODS HOLE) - PERTUSSIS VACCINE, 1989-1994 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9246 - UNION OF CONCERNED SCIENTISTS - EFFECTS OF POPULATION GROWTH ON GLOBAL RESOURCES, 1992-1994 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9249 - INCLEN, INC. - WORKSHOP ON ISSUES AND METHODOLOGY IN REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1992-1995 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9250 - RENE DUBOS CENTER FOR HUMAN ENVIRONMENTS, INC. - FORUM ON POPULATION, ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1994 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9250 - RENE DUBOS CENTER FOR HUMAN ENVIRONMENTS, INC. - FORUM ON POPULATION, ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2989)
    - PS 9252 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - POPULATION GROWTH AND ENVIRONMENT IN HIMALAYAS, 1992-1993 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9253 - TATA ENERGY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - WORKSHOP ON POPULATION AND NATURAL RESOURCES, 1992-1993 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9254 - CENTER FOR POPULATION OPTIONS - REPORT ON EXPERIENCES, 1992-1993 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9255 - PATHFINDER INTERNATIONAL - REPORT ON PAST WORK IN ADOLESCENT REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1992-1994; 2 folders. (Box R2989)
    - PS 9257 - CENTRE FOR DEVELOPMENT AND POPULATION ACTIVITIES - WOMEN IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1987-1994 (Box R2989)
    - PS 9258 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - REPRODUCTIVE RIGHTS IN INTERNATIONAL LAW, 1992-1994 (Box R2990)
  - International Philanthropy (IP)
    - IP 9201 - BADI FOUNDATION - RURAL DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1993 (Box R2990)
    - IP 9202 - ASHOKA: INNOVATORS FOR THE PUBLIC - CITIZEN BASE INITIATIVE OF ASHOKA FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1992-1993 (Box R2990)
  - International Security (IS)
    - IS 9108 - NATURAL RESOURCES DEFENSE COUNCIL - SOVIET PLUTONIUM SAFEGUARDS PROJECT, 1991-1994 (Box R2990)
    - IS 9201 - CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF SOVIET CHANGE - SOVIET NUCLEAR PROLIFERATION PROJECT, 1992-1993 (Box R2990)
    - IS 9203 - MONTEREY INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - BALLISTIC MISSILE DATABASE, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R2990)
    - IS 9206 - COUNCIL FOR RESPONSIBLE GENETICS - BIOLOGICAL WEAPONS THREAT, 1991-1992, 1996; 2 folders. (Box R2990)
    - IS 9208 - AFRICA LEADERSHIP FOUNDATION - AFRICA LEADERSHIP FORUM, 1988-1992, 1996 (Box R2990)
    - IS 9208 - AFRICA LEADERSHIP FOUNDATION - AFRICA LEADERSHIP FORUM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2991)
    - IS 9209 - ALBERT EINSTEIN PEACE PRIZE FOUNDATION - PARTICIPATION OF K. SUB RAHMANYAM AT CONFERENCE, 1992-1993 (Box R2991)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - SIE 8964 - EARTHVIEW FOUNDATION - PUBLIC ATTITUDE IN PLANETARY SECURITY, 1989-1995 (Box R2991)
    - SIE 8971 - FUND FOR EDUCATION IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1989-1993 (Box R2991)
    - SIE 9109 - NEW YORK COMMUNITY TRUST - FUND FOR NEW CITIZENS, 1991-1993 (Box R2991)
    - SIE 9111 - WASHINGTON CENTER FOR CHINA STUDIES, INC. - "CHINA REPORT" & SURVEY, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R2991)
    - SIE 9119 - ROCKEFELLER ARCHIVE CENTER - "PHILANTHROPY IN THE AFRICAN AMERICAN EXPERIENCE" CONFERENCE, 1991-1994 (Box R2991)
    - SIE 9143 - RAND CORPORATION - "REDUCING INNER-CITY DRUG MARKETS AND VIOLENCE", 1990-1996 (Box R2991)
    - SIE 9144 - STOCKHOLM UNIVERSITY - TODAY LITERARY MAGAZINE, 1990-1991, 1996 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9145 - LATINO ISSUES FORUM - LATINET, 1991, 1996 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9147 - FRIENDS OF INSTITUTE FOR A DEMOCRATIC ALTERNATIVE FOR SOUTH AFRICA, INC. - RECRUITING STAFF ECONOMIST, 1991-1995 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9149 - LAWYER'S COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS UNDER LAW - ENVIRONMENTAL JUSTICE ALLIANCE, 1991-1995 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9206 - SOUTH BRONX 2000 LOCAL DEVELOPMENT CORP. - ENVIRONMENTAL ENTERPRISES ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1991-1995 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9207 - AMERICAN DOCUMENTARY, INC. - MINORITY INVESTMENT FUND FOR FILM AND VIDEO, 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9208 - KARLSTROM, BO - INTERNATIONAL PRIVATE CAPITAL AND DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9209 - FILM ARTS FOUNDATION - AHISMA, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9211 - TAKE IT BACK FOUNDATION - MUNICIPAL RECYCLING AND REMANUFACTURING, 1992-1993 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9212 - ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN UNIVERSITIES- HIGHER EDUCATION COLLOQUIUM ON SCIENCE FACILITIES, 1991-1993 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9214 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY- "THE ECONOMICS OF TRANSITION", 1992-1994 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9215 - BELOIT COLLEGE - PRESERVATION OF NEGATIVES ORIENTAL EDUCATION COMMISSION EXPEDITION, 1991-1993 (Box R2992)
    - SIE 9216 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - SURVEY OF CHINESE STUDENTS IN U.S., 1992-1994 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9218 - AMERICAN INDIAN COLLEGE FUND, 1990-1993 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9219 - SOCIETY FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF WOMEN'S HEALTH RESEARCH - REGIONAL ROUNDTABLES ON WOMEN IN MEDICINE, 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9220 - NEW DEPARTURES, INC. - RECONSTRUCTION MAGAZINE, 1990-1992, 1996 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9223 - NEW IMAGES PRODUCTIONS, INC. - "SIMPLE JUSTICE", 1992-1993 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9224 - FAMILIES AND WORK INSTITUTE - "NATIONAL STUDY OF CHANGING WORKFORCE", 1992-1994 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9228 - COMMITIEE ON THE CONSTITUTIONAL SYSTEM - CONFERENCE AND PUBLICATION, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9229 - GRADUATE SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY CENTER OF CUNY - EVALUATING U.S. VOTER REGISTRATION SYSTEMS, 1992-1994 (Box R2993)
    - SIE 9230 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN - MOVE TOWARDS SELF-SUFFICIENCY, 1992-1996 (Box R2994)
    - SIE 9231 - FOUNDATION FOR SOCIAL INNOVATIONS USA - CIVIL SOCIETY LEADERSHIP FELLOWS PROGRAM, 1992-1994 (Box R2994)
    - SIE 9232 - NEW 42ND STREET, INC. - NEW VICTORY THEATRE, 1992-1993 (Box R2994)
    - SIE 9237 - ACADEMY FOR EDUCATIONAL DEVELOPMENT - ESTABLISH NATIONAL PUBLIC BROADCASTING ARCHIVES, 1992-1994 (Box R2994)
    - SIE 9238 - COUNCIL ON OCEAN LAW- GENERAL SUPPORT, 1992, 1996 (Box R2994)
    - SIE 9239 - INSTITUTE FOR SUSTAINABLE COMMUNITIES - COMMUNITY ENVIRONMENTAL ACTION PROJECT IN HUNGARY, 1992-1993 (Box R2994)
  - Special Programming (SP)
    - SP 8714 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - AGRICULTURAL PERFORMANCE OF AFRICAN COUNTRIES, 1987-1991, 1996 (Box R2994)
    - SP 8820 - NDEGWA, PHILIP, 1988-1992, 1996 (Box R2994)
    - SP 8831 - EISENHOWER MEDICAL RESEARCH AND EDUCATION CENTER - STRUCTURAL BIOLOGY RESEARCH COMMUNICATION NETWORK, 1988-1989, 1994 (Box R2994)
    - SP 9009 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY- TEACHING THROUGH TECHNOLOGY, 1990-1993 (Box R2994)
    - SP 9011 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - INTER-GENERATIONAL ECOLOGY CONFERENCE IN KENYA, 1990-1995 (Box R2994)
    - SP 8839 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY (MIT) - DEBT RELIEF AGENDA FOR THE 1990s - CONFERENCE, 1988, 1990, 1995 (Box R2995)
  - African Initiatives (AI)
    - AI 9104 - PEOPLE-CENTERED DEVELOPMENT FORUM - COMMUNICATIONS OUTREACH PROGRAM, 1991-1995 (Box R2994)
    - AI 9106 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - REDESIGN AFRICAN FELLOWSHIP PROGRAMS, 1991-1993, 1996 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9111 - MANOFF GROUP, INC. - INTERNATIONAL NUTRITION COUNCIL, 1991-1996 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9202 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND (UNICEF) - CONFERENCE ON EDUCATION FOR GIRLS, 1992, 1996 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9203 - INSTITUTE FOR A NEW SOUTH AFRICA - U.S.-SOUTH AFRICA SISTER COMMUNITY PROJECT, 1990-1992, 1996 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9205 - PRINCETON UNIVERSITY- INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT COOPERATION AND GLOBAL WOMEN'S MOVEMENT, 1992-1995 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9206 - AFRICAN WOMEN DEVELOPMENT AND COMMUNICATION NETWORK (FEMNET) - PROGRAMMING CONFERENCE, 1992-1994 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9210 - INTERNATIONAL FEDERATION OF LIBRARY ASSOCIATIONS AND INSTITUTIONS (IFLA) - PAN-AFRICAN CONFERENCE ON PRESERVATION AND ARCHIVING, 1992-1993 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9211 - WORLD LEARNING, INC.- REVIEW OF ORAP-SIT PROGRAM, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9218 - NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF LESOTHO - CONFERENCE: WOMEN AND DEVELOPMENT IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1992-1993 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9219 - AFRICAN-AMERICAN INSTITUTE, INC. - SOUTH AFRICAN OFFICE, 1991-1996 (Box R2995)
    - AI 9222 - HEALTH SYSTEMS TRUST - LINKAGE WITH NATIONAL EPIDEMIOLOGY BOARDS, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R2995)
  - School Reform (SR)
    - SR 9201 - WILLIAMS, BRUCE EDWARD - CONSULTANCY GRANT, 1991-1994 (Box R2995)
    - SR 9202 - NATIONAL URBAN LEAGUE - LOCAL SCHOOL REFORM, 1989-1995 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9202 - NATIONAL URBAN LEAGUE - LOCAL SCHOOL REFORM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2996)
    - SR 9203 - CALIFORNIA SCHOOL BOARDS FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE ON OPPORTUNITIES FOR HISPANIC STUDENTS, 1992-1993 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9204 - GRAY, LYNN- "A SECOND RENAISSANCE: RETHINKING EDUCATION" CONFERENCE, 1992 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9206 - WINSTEN, JAY A. - DEVELOP AND TEST A CHILDREN'S IMPACT STATEMENT (CIS) (CONSULTING AGREEMENT), 1991-1994 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9207 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - QUALITY EDUCATION ACT EFFECTS ON AT-RISK CHILDREN, 1991-1994 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9209 - NEW YORK COMMUNITY TRUST/COMMUNITY FUNDS, INC. - NEW YORK CITY PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM GOVERNANCE STRUCTURE REFORM, 1992, 1995 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9211 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - SECOND MEETING OF SCHOOL REFORM LEADERS, 1992-1994 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9212 - THE FUND FOR PUBLIC SCHOOLS, INC. - LATINO COMMISSION ON EDUCATIONAL REFORM, 1992-1994 (Box R2996)
    - SR 9213 - TEXAS INTERFAITH EDUCATION FUND - PARTICIPANTS ATTENDANCE AT CONFERENCE: "HOPE FOR AMERICA'S SCHOOLS", 1992-1993 (Box R2997)
    - SR 9214 - URBAN STRATEGIES COUNCIL - COMMISSION FOR POSITIVE CHANGE IN THE OAKLAND PUBLIC SCHOOLS, 1990-1995 (Box R2997)
    - SR 9215 - COMMUNITY FOUNDATION OF GREATER WASHINGTON - PRODUCTION AND DISTRIBUTION OF "STOP THE VIOLENCE" VIDEO, 1992, 1995 (Box R2997)
    - SR 9218 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - GRADUATE SCHOOLS OF EDUCATION PROJECT, 1991-1993 (Box R2997)
    - SR 9220 - COUNCIL ON FOUNDATIONS - PRECOLLEGIATE EDUCATION PROGRAM, 1990-1994 (Box R2997)
    - SR 9221 - GORDON, EDMUND W., 1990-1995 (Box R2997)
    - SR 9222 - VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY - BRINGING RESEARCH TO POLICY AND PRACTICE THROUGH TELECOMMUNICATIONS SEMINARS, 1992-1994 (Box R2997)
    - SR 9223 - COUNCIL OF THE GREAT CITY SCHOOLS, SUPPORT PUBLICATION "NATIONAL URBAN EDUCATION GOALS: BASELINE INDICATORS, 1990-91", 1992-1993 (Box R2997)
  - Health Sciences (HS)
    - HS 9110 - UN - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION ? OUTPATIENT SERVICES MEETING, 1991-1996 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9202 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL- "PARTNERS FOR SAFE MOTHERHOOD" MEETING, 1991-1993 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9203 - BRITISH COLUMBIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - CLINICAL & DIAGNOSTIC SURVEY IN CAMEROON, 1991-1993 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9206 - WORLD BANK - BC CONFERENCE: "HEALTH TRANSITION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES - SECTOR PRIORITIES AND REFORM", 1991-1994 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9207 - UNIVERSIDAD DEL VALLE- FACULTAD DE SALUD'S MEDICAL LIBRARIES UPDATE, 1991-1995 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9209 - STUDENT PUGWASH USA - 1992 INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON HEALTH CARE IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1991-1994 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9211 - TASK FORCE FOR CHILD SURVIVAL AND DEVELOPMENT - INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON PUBLIC HEALTH SURVEILLANCE, 1992-1993 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9212 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - HEALTH SCIENCES - PROGRAM OPERATIONS - XIII INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS FOR TROPICAL MEDICINE AND MALARIA, 1992 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9217 - D. I. IVANOVSKY INSTITUTE OF VIROLOGY - DEVELOPING COUNTRY PARTICIPATION IN SYMPOSIUM, 1992-1994 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9218 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY - STRENGTHEN INSTITUTE OF PUBLIC HEALTH, 1992 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9220 - WARACHIT, PAIJIT - SITE VISITS RELATED TO REGULATORY ISSUES / DENGUE VACCINE IN THAILAND, 1992 (Box R2998)
    - HS 9222 - AGA KHAN FOUNDATION, U.S.A. - MAP, 1989-1993, 1996; 2 folders. (Box R2999)
    - HS 9222 - AGA KHAN FOUNDATION, U.S.A. - MAP - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R2999)
    - HS 9223 - ASOCIACION PARA LA INVESTIGACION DE LA SALUD (ASINSA)- BOOK, "CHOLERA AND HYGIENE", 1992 (Box R2999)
    - HS 9232 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY- CHILDREN'S VACCINE INITIATIVE MEASLES PROJECT, 1992-1993 (Box R2999)
    - HS 9236 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - DATA ANALYSIS ON GROWTH MONITORING FOR YOUNG CHILDREN IN SOUTHERN INDIA, 1991-1994 (Box R2999)
    - HS 9237 - AMERICAN ACADEMY OF PEDIATRICS - SUPPORT PARTICIPANTS AT MEETING ON INTERNATIONAL CHILD HEALTH CURRICULUM, 1992-1997 (Box R3000)
      Records more than 20 years old are open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Entire file open in 2018. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - HS 9238 - PAN-AFRICAN SOCIETY OF CARDIOLOGY- CONGRESS ON PREVENTIVE CARDIOLOGY IN AFRICA, 1992-1993 (Box R3000)
    - HS 9249 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - WORKSHOP: "GIVING VOICE TO CHILDREN: STRENGTHENING ADVOCACY FOR CHILD HEALTH AND WELL-BEING", 1992-1993; 2 folders. (Box R3000)
    - HS 9251 - EDUCATIONAL COMMISSION FOR FOREIGN MEDICAL GRADUATES, 1985-1993, 1996 (Box R3000)
    - HS 9253 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - RE-EVALUATION AND PLANNING FOR PUBLIC HEALTH TRAINING AND RESEARCH, 1992-1993, 1996; 3 folders. (Box R3000)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 86067 A 25 - OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY - DEMOGRAPHIC TRAINING, 1980-1996 (Box R3001)
    - RF 86068 A 51 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - GOSSYPOL EFFECTS ON FREE RADICAL FORMATION, 1986-1992, 1996 (Box R3001)
    - RF 87005 A 54 - NYINDO, MRAMBA B. A., 1984-1992 (Box R3001)
    - RF 87005 A 64 - RAO, M. R. S., 1987-1990, 1994 (Box R3001)
    - RF 87031 A 20 - OPERATIONS RESEARCH GROUP (INDIA) ? BIHAR FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES, 1987-1995 (Box R3001)
    - RF 87033 - SOCIAL SCIENCE TRAINING IN INCLEN, 1987 (Box R3001)
    - RF 87040 - KAGISO TRUST - BLACK LEADERSHIP IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1986-1994; 4 folders. (Box R3002)
    - RF 87047 - IITA/CIAT - CASSAVA IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1989-1993 (Box R3002)
    - RF 87047 - IITA/CIAT - CASSAVA IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1985-1988; 2 folders (Box R3003)
    - RF 87067 - INFORMATION ACCESS AND HEALTH POLICY, 1985-1992, 1996 (Box R3003)
    - RF 88009 A 37 - UNIVERSITY OF GUADALAJARA - GOSSYPOL EFFECT IN MEN WITH HIV, 1988-1993 (Box R3003)
    - RF 88009 A 38 - ASSIUT UNIVERSITY- VAGINAL VS. ORAL CONTRACEPTIVES, 1989-1993 (Box R3004)
    - RF 88024 - FOUNDATION CENTER - INFORMATION SERVICES, 1987-1993; 4 folders. (Box R3004)
    - RF 88045 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - REPRODUCTIVE AND DEVELOPMENTAL BIOLOGY, 1991 May-1996 (Box R3004)
    - RF 88045 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - REPRODUCTIVE AND DEVELOPMENTAL BIOLOGY, 1987-1991 April (Box R3005)
    - RF 88048 A 89 - GENDER ROLE CHANGES - ASSESSMENT, 1985-1993 (Box R3005)
    - RF 88048 A 89 - GENDER ROLE CHANGES - ASSESSMENT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3005)
    - RF 88072 A 11 - EMORY UNIVERSITY - AFRICA GOVERNANCE, 1989-1993 (Box R3006)
    - RF 88072 A 13 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - AFRICAN STUDIES, 1987-1994 (Box R3006)
    - RF 88072 A 14 - AFRICARE - CONSTITUENCY FOR AFRICA, 1991-1994 (Box R3006)
    - RF 88078 A 60 - UNIVERSITY OF YAOUNDE - CAMEROON WOMEN & CONTRACEPTIVES, 1987-1992, 1996 (Box R3006)
    - RF 88079 A 257 - OPERATIONS RESEARCH GROUP (INDIA) - STATUS OF WOMEN & DEMOGRAPHIC CHANGE IN UTTAR PRADESH, 1987-1993 (Box R3006)
    - RF 88086 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE- ZIMBABWE IRRIGATION EVALUATION, 1988-1994; 2 folders. (Box R3007)
    - RF 89013 - EDUCATIONAL BROADCASTING CORP. - WORLD DANCE, 1986-1994 (Box R3007)
    - RF 89013 - EDUCATIONAL BROADCASTING CORP. - WORLD DANCE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3007)
    - RF 89014 A 443 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS (AUSTIN) - RESIDENT FELLOWS (MIDDLE EAST), 1988-1993 (Box R3007)
    - RF 89014 A 444 - HUNTER COLLEGE - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1988-1993, 1996 (Box R3007)
    - RF 89014 A 447 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1985-1993 (Box R3008)
    - RF 89014 A 450 - CENTER FOR PSYCHOSOCIAL STUDIES - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1989-1993 (Box R3008)
    - RF 89014 A 450 - CENTER FOR PSYCHOSOCIAL STUDIES - RESIDENT FELLOWS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3008)
    - RF 89014 A 451 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS (AFRICANA), 1989-1993 (Box R3008)
    - RF 89014 A 452 - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1993-1997 (Box R3009)
    - RF 89026 A 21 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY- DISEASE RESISTANCE, 1989-1993, 1996 (Box R3009)
    - RF 89026 A 22 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY- LECTIN ENHANCED NITROGEN FIXATION, 1989-1993 (Box R3009)
    - RF 89026 A 26 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY- PHOTOPERIOD SENSITIVITY, 1989-1994 (Box R3009)
    - RF 89026 A 28 - UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD - GENETIC TRANSPOSABLE ELEMENTS, 1989-1993, 1996 (Box R3009)
    - RF 89026 A 30 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY- VARIETAL IMPROVEMENT FOR HIGHER PROTEIN CONTENT, 1989-1994 (Box R3009)
    - RF 89027 A 10 - STANFORD UNIVERSITY - BARTON, 1989-1994 (Box R3009)
    - RF 89029 A 184 - SUEZ CANAL UNIVERSITY - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY - EL SAYED, 1988-1989, 1993 (Box R3010)
    - RF 89033 A 44 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR POPULATION SCIENCES (INDIA) - BIRTH INTERVALS & FERTILITY, 1989-1994 (Box R3010)
    - RF 89033 A 48 - UNIVERSITY OF BUENOS AIRES - REPRODUCTIVE ABNORMALITIES IN DIABETIC RATS, 1990-1992 (Box R3010)
    - RF 89033 A 50 - PAULISTA MEDICAL SCHOOL - HORMONES & SERTOLI CELL, 1989-1996 (Box R3010)
    - RF 89034 A 86 - IYAM, DAVID URU, 1988-1997 (Box R3010)
    - RF 89034 A 141 - CHESEREM, SALINA J., 1989-1993 (Box R3010)
    - RF 89043 - BETTER BABIES PROJECT, INC. - LOW BIRTH RATE, 1986-1993 (Box R3010)
    - RF 89043 - BETTER BABIES PROJECT, INC. - LOW BIRTH RATE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3010)
    - RF 89050 A 7 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE (WRI) - BC CONFERENCE: STRENGTHENING ENVIRONMENTAL CAPABILITIES, 1990-1991 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89055 A 42 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (IITA) - "TIME AND SPACE" WORKSHOP, 1989-1993 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 93 - ESPINOZA ESQUIVEL, ANA M., 1989-1996 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 100 - REINACH, FERNANDO DE CASTRO, 1990-1993 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 104 - OJEH, CLEMENT KANYIDINMA, 1984-1992, 1996 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 105 - ARAMBURO DE LA HOZ, CARLOS, 1989-1996 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 108 - EL-AWADY, MOSTAFA KAMEL, 1989-1994 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 113 - SONTHAYANON, BURACHAI, 1990-1994 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 119 - OLIVEIRA, DULCE ELEONORA DE, 1990-1994 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 124 - KIM KYOON EON, 1990-1994 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 127 - GHALIB, HASHIM WARSAMA, 1991 (Box R3011)
    - RF 88057 A 128 - VIJAYA, S., 1991-1994 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 129 - LOPEZ, EDUARDO L, 1991-1996 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89057 A 130 - PRADO, DAVID, 1991, 1995 (Box R3011)
    - RF 89064 A 26 - CAIRO DEMOGRAPHIC CENTRE - FAMILY PLANNING SERVICES IN EGYPT, 1990-1994 (Box R3012)
    - RF 89064 A 28 - POPULATION COUNCIL, INC. - FAMILY PLANNING INTERNATIONAL RESEARCH, 1990-1993 (Box R3012)
    - RF 89064 A 30 - UNIVERSITY OF DHAKA - FAMILY PLANNING IN BANGLADESH, 1987-1993 (Box R3012)
    - RF 89064 A 34 - FAMILY PLANNING PROGRAM EVALUATION IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES - THAILAND WORKSHOP, 1993-1994; 2 folders. (Box R3012)
    - RF 89068 - WGBH EDUCATIONAL FOUNDATION - "OTHER AMERICAS" TV SERIES, 1987-1994 (Box R3012)
    - RF 89068 - WGBH EDUCATIONAL FOUNDATION - "OTHER AMERICAS" TV SERIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3012)
    - RF 89076 A 6 - AMERICAN FILM INSTITUTE - HOME VIDEO MARKET DISTRIBUTION, 1990-1993 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89076 A 9 - MODERN LANGUAGE ASSOCIATION OF AMERICA - VIDEO USE IN U.S. COLLEGES SURVEY, 1990, 1993-1994 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89092 A 71 - COMMONWEALTH REGIONAL HEALTH COMMUNITY SECRETARIAT FOR EAST, CENTRAL & SOUTHERN AFRICA - MATERNAL MORTALITY RISK FACTORS, 1990-1994 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89092 A 77 - MHOZYA, XAVIER M., 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89092 A 78 - PALLONI, ALBERTO, 1990-1994 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89092 A 83 - BRADLEY, CANDICE, 1990-1993 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89092 A 85 - BROWN, CHARLES KWEKU, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89094 A 1 - SCHAEFERS, GEORGE A., 1990-1993 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89096 - SOIL FERTILITY IN AFRICA, 1988-1990 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89096 A 4 - EDINBURGH SCHOOL OF AGRICULTURE - AGROTECHNOLOGY, 1989-1996 (Box R3013)
    - RF 89096 A 7 - OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY - TROPICAL SOIL AND WATER MANAGEMENT, 1989-1994 (Box R3013)